SHENDI TEUKU MAULANA EFENDI

JUNIOR DATA ANALYST

shendyteuku2@gmail.com

+62 895-1485-1100

Madiun, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Profile Summary

I am a 4th semester student who has experience studying in the Oracle Academy Digital Talent Kominfo batch 2 program and has made a Bookstore application project using Java and MySQL and I joined BEM as a division secretary which made me an active, communicative, confident person, can work in teams and can use several editing applications.

Professional Skill -

Relevant Skill

- Data Analysis
- Statistics and Math
- Programming • Data Visualization
- Communication
- Perseverance and Rigor
- Problem-Solving
 Curiosity and Will to Learn

Education

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering PGRI Madiun University

2021-Now

Informatics Engineering students focus on various subjects including programming, database, computer networks, etc.

Science Department of SMA Negeri 2 Madiun

2017-2020

Science Department students focus on various subjects including learning science, statistics and math.

Work Experience

Freelance Graphic Design

2021

- Plan and develop effective social media strategies to achieve company goals.
- Actively interact with followers and audiences through comments, direct messages and prompt responses to build good relationships.

Proffesional Player 2020 - 2021

- Has won major tournaments, one of which represented Madiun city in the mayor's cup and was covered by JawaPos.
- Have expert communication with the team.

Organization Experience

Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa (BEM)

Now

Secretary of the Ministry of Communication and Information

- Coordinating internal communication.
- Organizing and coordinating internal meetings.
- Successfully implemented several work programs including BEM design and attributes, optimization of BEM social media.

Design and Documentation of Unipma's 48th Anniversary (2023)

- As a Putra-Putri Unipma workshop operator.
- Responsible for the publication, decoration and documentation of Unipma's 48th Anniversary.

Department Of Informatics (DEPTICS)

2022-Now

Multimedia Division (2022-2023)

- As Multimedia Division Staff.
- Multimedia Editing.
- Digital Platform Management.
- Multimedia Project Management.
- Coordination with Creative Team.

Project Experience

- Final Project build applications using Java with OOP and MVC.
- Head of the Student Creativity Program "Duokids Sebagai Sarana Belajar Bahasa Inggris untuk Anak".
- Student Organization Capacity Building Program "Inovasi Objek Wisata Sendang Sentul Berbasis Pelestarian Budaya Guna Meningkatkan Ekonomi Sebagai Pengembangan Daya Tarik Wisata Desa Ngendut Kabupaten Ponorogo".
- Final Project Database Design and Database Programming Oracle Academy

Ability

- Java
- Canva
- C++
- Tableu
- MySQL
- Microsoft Office
- phpMyAdmin

Interest

• Data analyst

· Managing social media

Creating graphic design